<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unity3d on Raj Pathare</title>
    <link>https://rajpathare.com/tags/unity3d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unity3d on Raj Pathare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rajpathare.com/tags/unity3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angry Meteor</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/angrymeteor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/angrymeteor/</guid>
      <description>AngryMeteor AngryMeteor is a hypercasual game, where you need to save your planet from a meteor shower.
Link Game Demo Developer  Raj Pathare  Platforms  Android (v4.1+) PC  Graphics/Textures The game graphics are specially designed for mobile users. The textures are chosen in such a way that the users may not experience any lag while playing the game.
Future work To add more features in the game like - powerups, adding more custom levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARNotes</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/arnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/arnotes/</guid>
      <description>An AR-based Piano(Keyboard) app which responds to your real-time key press .
 Download the app here  Steps to be followed  Take a print-out of the given piano (image),it is recommmended to take a medium-sized print for better usability.   Download and install the application,the dropbox link for the same is provided above. After installing the application,open it and focus your camera on the print-out (the piano). Press the keys and enjoy playing your favourite instrument with some added twist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity3D Resources</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/resource/unityresources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/resource/unityresources/</guid>
      <description>Sites  Unity Official Site: Start bringing your vision to life today. Unitys real-time 3D development platform empowers you with all you need to create, operate, and monetize. Unity learn - Raywenderlich: In this Unity learning path for beginners, you will learn the fundamental techniques in Unity development, such as Animation, Sound, Particle Systems, Scripting, UI, and much more. Unity3D for Absolute Beginners: New to Unity? You should definetely check this site out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
