<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raj Pathare</title>
    <link>https://rajpathare.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Raj Pathare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rajpathare.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angry Meteor</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/angrymeteor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/angrymeteor/</guid>
      <description>AngryMeteor AngryMeteor is a hypercasual game, where you need to save your planet from a meteor shower.
Link Game Demo Developer  Raj Pathare  Platforms  Android (v4.1+) PC  Graphics/Textures The game graphics are specially designed for mobile users. The textures are chosen in such a way that the users may not experience any lag while playing the game.
Future work To add more features in the game like - powerups, adding more custom levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARNotes</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/arnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/arnotes/</guid>
      <description>An AR-based Piano(Keyboard) app which responds to your real-time key press .
 Download the app here  Steps to be followed  Take a print-out of the given piano (image),it is recommmended to take a medium-sized print for better usability.   Download and install the application,the dropbox link for the same is provided above. After installing the application,open it and focus your camera on the print-out (the piano). Press the keys and enjoy playing your favourite instrument with some added twist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChitChat</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/chitchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/chitchat/</guid>
      <description>ChitChat ChitChat is a chat application where users can join and chat in different rooms. Socket.io is used for connecting different users together.
 Check the website here  Screenshots About the project  Type in your username and the desired room that you wish to enter. If the room doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, it will be created when you type in a new room. You can see the users present in the room and chat with them / send them your location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID19-Tracker</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/covid19tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/covid19tracker/</guid>
      <description>About the project -  This site lets you track the new coronavirus (COVID-19). Since the data is public, it can be fetched easily. The JSON data gets updated every 30mins.  Check the website here
Screenshot - Technologies used - Reactjs, netlify(Hosting) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games Bond</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/gamesbond/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/gamesbond/</guid>
      <description>Games Bond A simple website(front-end) , where you can access a bunch of flash games.
Check the website here
Screenshots About the project  You can play different flash games here. This was my first web project. I wanted to learn HTML/CSS.  Technologies used:  HTML5, CSS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyrics-finder</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/projects/lyrics-finder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/projects/lyrics-finder/</guid>
      <description>Lyrics-finder Find the lyrics for any song! Made with Reactjs and context-api
 Check the website here  Screenshots About the project  The website can be used to find lyrics for any song. Type in a song title and the list of all matching songs will be listed. This was my first Reactjs project. I wanted to learn reactjs and was curious about the working of context-api.  Technologies used:  Reactjs, context-api, Bootstrap  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some cool blogs</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/resource/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/resource/blogs/</guid>
      <description>Sites  Hacker News: Hacker News keeps me updated about the recent trends in industry. The Verge: Another cool site which keeps me updated about upcoming tech. TechCrunch: Anything and everything you need to know about tech, you can find it here. VentureBeat: This is probably the best place to read about funded startups, if you’re deep in the startup/vc scene this is a great place to get your tech news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity3D Resources</title>
      <link>https://rajpathare.com/resource/unityresources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:15:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajpathare.com/resource/unityresources/</guid>
      <description>Sites  Unity Official Site: Start bringing your vision to life today. Unitys real-time 3D development platform empowers you with all you need to create, operate, and monetize. Unity learn - Raywenderlich: In this Unity learning path for beginners, you will learn the fundamental techniques in Unity development, such as Animation, Sound, Particle Systems, Scripting, UI, and much more. Unity3D for Absolute Beginners: New to Unity? You should definetely check this site out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
